Over the next few months Matt,
在接下来的几个月里 Matt,
Luis and I will be your primary instructors.
路易斯和我将是你们的主要导师
There will also, occasionally,
偶尔也会有,
be some other experts who come in to teach topics that they specialize in.
成为其他专家来教授他们专长的课题
A little bit about me.
一点关于我的事
I've been a teacher for a while,
我当了一段时间的老师,
having started teaching programming when I was
我从岁开始教程序设计
completing my Masters in Electrical Engineering at Stanford.
在斯坦福大学攻读电子工程硕士学位
I focused on learning about medical systems and first
我专注于学习医疗系统
got into deep learning as a tool for medical diagnostics.
进入深度学习领域 成为医学诊断的工具
I'm happiest when I'm creating and learning,
我最开心的时候就是创造和学习,
and so I'm also very into deep learning as it's used in artistic applications
所以我也非常喜欢深度学习 因为它被用于艺术应用
like learning to imitate the style of an artist
就像学习模仿艺术家的风格
or to generate new kinds of images entirely.
或者完全生成新类型的图像
I'm a former physicist,
我以前是物理学家,
former neuroscientist and a current huge fan of all things data.
前神经科学家 现在是所有数据的狂热爱好者
I've been working with Python and data in general for the past nine years.
在过去的九年里 我一直在使用 Python 和一般的数据
During my PhD work,
在我攻读博士学位期间,
I used machine learning models to classify electrical signals from neurons.
我使用机器学习模型对神经元的电信号进行分类
I have also created a few Python data science libraries,
我还创建了一些 Python 数据科学库,
a Bayesian data analysis package called Sample,
一个名为 Sample 的贝叶斯数据分析包,
and SQL, SQL for data analysts.
数据分析师使用 SQL 和 SQL
I'm fascinated by deep learning because automation is the future,
我着迷于深度学习 因为自动化是未来,
and deep learning is the future of automation.
深度学习是自动化的未来
I'm a pure mathematician and a former Google engineer.
我是一个纯粹的数学家 也曾是谷歌的工程师
During my PhD, I worked an algebraic combinatorics,
在读博士期间我在代数组合学工作,
a field in which theoretical mathematics and applied probability meet.
理论数学和应用概率相遇的领域
I then spent some years in academia working on research and teaching at university.
后来我在学术界花了几年时间在大学里从事研究和教学工作
This is where I fell in love with machine learning and I
这就是我爱上机器学习的地方
decided to switch to Google where I worked in
我决定跳槽到我工作的谷歌
the team that uses machine learning algorithms to generate YouTube video recommendations.
这个团队使用机器学习算法生成 YouTube 视频推荐
I, too, find deep learning fascinating as it combines
我也觉得深度学习很吸引人 因为它结合了
theoretical beauty with powerful applications
具有强大应用的理论之美.
最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6